# **Andrew Zinski**

### Student

804-839-8072 | andrew@zinski.net | 2730 Bosham LN, Midlothian, VA 23113

## **Summary**

In my career I have worked predominantly in vehicle maintenance and repairs. my experience in this includes electrical repair, bodywork, engine replacement, and safety inspections. Currently I am a student at the University of Richmond to become a full stack web developer.

#### Credentials

Certified Safety Inspector, State of Virginia

2019

## Experience

Lead Tire Technician, McLaren Cooperation, Lynchburg, VA	2015-2016
Cashier/Service Writer, Walmart, Bedford, VA	2016-2018
Fleet Maintenance Technician/Aircraft Mechanic, McLaren Cooperation, Lynchburg, VA	2018-2020

### Education

Highschool diploma, Timberlake Christian Schools, Forest, VA	2012—2016
Full stack Web Developer, University of Richmond, Richmond, VA	2020-present

#### **Affiliations**

Civil Air Patrol 2013–2015

# **Community Service**

Volunteer Worker, Calvary Baptist church, Lynchburg, VA

2013-2016

As a Volunteer, some of my services included House cleaning, maintenance and painting for those not able to do so, Catering for The Boys and Girls club in downtown Lynchburg, and caroling for those in assisted living.

Library volunteer, Forest public Library, Forest, VA

2015

During the summer I volunteer at my local library and helped the librarians with their duties.